const QUESTION_U2 = [
  { id:'2usa1',
  rulelink:'1084334-rule-201-composition-of-teams',
  rulenum:'201b',//checked
    question: 'During the course of a game, a team no longer has a properly registered coach available to them on the bench and adult supervision cannot be found. The game must be forfeited',
    correctanswer:"False",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "True"
    ]
  },
  { id:'2usa2',
  rulelink:'1084652-rule-608-checking-from-behind',
  rulenum:'608c',//checked
    question: "A player checks an opponent from behind with excessive force while the opponent is in a vulnerable or defenseless position or the action was deemed to be a deliberate attempt to injure an opponent. The proper penalty is a Match Penalty",
    correctanswer:"True",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "False"
    ]
  },
  { id:'2usa3',
  rulelink:'1084483-rule-407-goalkeeper-penalties',
  rulenum:'407a',//checked
    question: 'Please indicate which player serves the penalty: Misconduct assessed to Goalkeeper.',
    correctanswer:"Player on the ice when the infraction occurred",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "Player on the bench (non goalkeeper) when the infraction",
      "Offending Player"
    ]
  },

  { id:'2usa4',
  rulelink:'1084338-rule-205-change-of-players',
  rulenum:'502c',//checked
    question: 'Please indicate the proper face-off location: Premature Goalie Substitution',
    correctanswer:"Center Ice Face-off spot",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "Neutral Zone Face-off spot",
      "End Zone Face-off spot"
    ]
  },
  { id:'2usa5',
  rulelink:'1085021-handling-puck-with-hands',
  rulenum:'Situation 4', //checked
    question: 'The puck is batted with the hand by an attacking player in their attacking zone, “deflecting” off the opposing goalkeeper. This is an immediate whistle.',
    correctanswer:"False",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "True"
    ]
  },
  { id:'2usa6',
  rulelink:'1084657-rule-612-face-off-locations',
  rulenum:'612c',//checked
    question: 'An attacking player in the attacking zone shoots the puck on goal. The puck deflects off the crossbar and goes directly out of play. The face-off takes place at:',
    correctanswer:"A face off spot in the attacking zone",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "A neutral zone face off spot",
      "The center ice face off spot"
    ]
  },
  { id:'2usa7',
  rulelink:'1084679-rule-627-kicking-opponent-or-puck',
  rulenum:'627a',//checked
    question: "A Match Penalty for Kicking shall be assessed to any player or goalkeeper who uses their skate to 'Push Off' an opponent.",
    correctanswer:"False",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "True"
    ]
  },
  { id:'2usa8',
  rulelink:'1084590-referee',
  rulenum:'Situation 6', //checked
    question: 'At the conclusion of the game, the official determines he/she has erred in assessing a checking from behind penalty and assessed a 5-minute major and a misconduct penalty, not a game misconduct penalty. The correct course of action is:',
    correctanswer:"File a supplemental discipline report",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "Cross off the misconduct and add the game misconduct at the bottom scoresheet",
      "Let the penalty stand as assessed and call the coach or team mgr"
    ]
  },
  { id:'2usa9',
  rulelink:'1084478-rule-402-minor-penalties',
  rulenum:'205b & 402b',//checked
    question: 'Please indicate which player serves the penalty: Minor Penalty for Too Many Players on the Ice',
    correctanswer:"Player on the ice when the infraction occurred",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "Player on the bench (non goalkeeper) when the infraction",
      "Offending Player"
    ]
  },

  { id:'2usa10',
  rulelink:'1084542-situation-6-charts',//checked
  rulenum:'Three players on the same team assessed a combination of minor and major penalties. “Sig.” = the infraction is being signaled by the Referee when the goal is scored.(Chart 3)',
    question: 'Team A is short-handed by one minor penalty. With play in progress, the Referee signals another minor penalty on Team A. Before play is stopped, Team B scores. The proper action is the minor penalty being served is terminated and the delayed penalty is assessed in the normal manner',
    correctanswer:"True",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "False"
    ]
  },
  { id:'2usa11',
  rulelink:'1084663-rule-615-fighting',
  rulenum:'615c', //checked
    question: 'A game misconduct penalty shall be assessed to any player whose helmet/facemask was not worn properly and comes off their head during an altercation',
    correctanswer:"True",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "False"
    ]
  },
  { id:'2usa12',
  rulelink:'1084675-rule-624-icing-the-puck',
  rulenum:'624b(1)',//checked
    question: 'A shorthanded team shall not be allowed to legally ice the puck at the 16 & Under level or below',
    correctanswer:"False",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "True"
    ]
  },
  { id:'2usa13',
  rulelink:'1084657-rule-612-face-off-locations',
  rulenum:'612d', //checked
    question: 'A stoppage of play in an end zone is followed by a gathering of players. The ensuing face off shall take place in the neutral zone if any of the attacking players enter the zone further than the outer edge of the face off circles',
    correctanswer:"True",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "False"
    ]
  },
  { id:'2usa14',
  rulelink:'1084973-abuse-of-officials-and-other-misconduct',
  rulenum:'Situation 7 & 601b(1)', //checked
    question: 'Which of the following would NOT result in a misconduct penalty?',
    correctanswer:"Profane language by the coach",
    incorrectanswers: [
      "Mouthpiece violation",
      "Player throws equipment out of the rink"
    ]
  },

{ id:'2usa15',
rulelink:'1084482-rule-406-penalty-shot',
rulenum:'406c',//checked
  question: 'Please indicate the proper face-off location: Unsuccessful Penalty shot attempt',
  correctanswer:"End Zone Face-off spot",
  incorrectanswers: [
    "Neutral Zone Face-off spot",
    "Center Ice Face-off spot"
  ]
},
{ id:'2usa16',
rulelink:'1084334-rule-201-composition-of-teams',
rulenum:'201a',//checked
  question: 'A team may dress (3) Goalkeepers and (17) skaters',
  correctanswer:"True",
  incorrectanswers: [
    "False"
  ]
},
{ id:'2usa17',
rulelink:'1084578-rule-501-appointment-of-officials',
rulenum:'501a',//checked
  question: 'The three-official system (one Referee/two Linesman) and the two-official system (two Referee’s) are the only approved systems for USA Hockey sanctioned games. Districts or Affiliates are authorized to use the four-official system (two Referee’s and two Linesman) for gamesinvolving teams in the Youth and Girls’ 16 & under age classifications and older (including High School and Adults).',
  correctanswer:"True",
  incorrectanswers: [
    "False"
  ]
},
{ id:'2usa18',
rulelink:'1084455-protective-equipment',
rulenum:'Situation 1',//checked
  question: 'Keeping safety as the primary consideration, the referee should stop play whenever the goalkeeper loses a glove and is in a vulnerable position, UNLESS there is an imminent scoring opportunity in which play should be allowed to continue until the imminent scoring opportunity has passed',
  correctanswer:"True",
  incorrectanswers: [
    "False"
  ]
},
{ id:'2usa19',
rulelink:'1084406-rule-308-electronic-devices',
rulenum:'308b',//checked
  question: "An electronic device may be used to challenge an official's call if the team uses its time-out to do so",
  correctanswer:"False",
  incorrectanswers: [
    "True"
  ]
},
{ id:'2usa20',
rulelink:'1084353-players-in-uniform',
rulenum:'Situation 4',//checked
  question: 'Players that are ineligible for the game should be crossed off the scoresheet at the conclusion of the game',
  correctanswer:"False",
  incorrectanswers: [
    "True"
  ]
},
{ id:'2usa21',
rulelink:'1084681-rule-628-kneeing',
rulenum:'628',//checked
  question: 'The penalty options for Kneeing an opponent are',
  correctanswer:"Minor or Major penalty. Major plus game misconduct if injury occurs",
  incorrectanswers: [
    "Minor plus misconduct", "Match Penalty"
  ]
},

{ id:'2usa22',
rulelink:'1084485-rule-408-delayed-penalties',
rulenum:'408c',//checked
  question: 'Two players from Team A are assessed non-coincidental penalties at the same time. Player 34 is assessed a minor and player 16 a major. Which penalty is recorded first?',
  correctanswer:"The minor penalty to Player 34.",
  incorrectanswers: [
    "The major penalty to Player 16.", "Captain’s choice as to which penalty."
  ]
},

{ id:'2usa23',
rulelink:'1084654-rule-610-delaying-the-game',
rulenum:'610c',//checked
  question: 'The puck is deliberately shot or batted out of play. This will result in:',
  correctanswer:"A minor penalty to the offending player or goalkeeper.",
  incorrectanswers: [
    "A face-off at the nearest face-off location.",
     "A face-off at the nearest face-off location with no change for the offending team."
  ]
},

{ id:'2usa24',
rulelink:'1084491-minor-penalties',
rulenum:'Situation 18',//checked
  question: 'Player A receives a minor penalty. Prior to the ensuing face-off, a Team B player receives a minor penalty. The two penalties are considered coincidental even though they were not committed at the same time',
  correctanswer:"True",
  incorrectanswers: [
    "False"
  ]
},
{ id:'2usa25',
rulelink:'1084666-rule-618-handling-puck-with-hands',
rulenum:'618a',//checked
  question: 'A player closes his hand on the puck and does not drop it immediately to the ice. The officials should:',
  correctanswer:"Stop play and conduct a last play face-off.",
  incorrectanswers: [
    "Assess the player a minor penalty for delay of game.",
     "Do nothing as long as the player does not take more than one stride."
  ]
},

{ id:'2usa26',
rulelink:'1084493-misconduct-penalties',
rulenum:'Situation 4', //checked
  question: 'During a Youth game, a player is assessed a non-coincident major plus game misconduct penalty and is removed from the game. Who must serve the major penalty and when must he enter the penalty bench',
  correctanswer:"Any non-penalized player (non goalkeeper) and must enter penalty bench immediately",
  incorrectanswers: [
    "Offending Player who must enter penalty bench immediately",
    "Player on the ice when the infraction occurred and must enter penalty bench prior to expiration of the major penalty"
  ]
},
{ id:'2usa27',
rulelink:'1084651-rule-607-charging',
rulenum:'607d(Note1)',//checked
  question: 'Any deliberate body contact or check that is delivered to the goalkeeper shall be penalized as charging',
  correctanswer:"True",
  incorrectanswers: [
    "False"
  ]
},
{ id:'2usa28',
rulelink:'1015130-zero-tolerance-policy',
rulenum:'ZERO TOLERANCE POLICY - Parents/Spectators', //checked
  question: 'An official is NOT allowed to stop a game if parents/spectators display inappropriate and disruptive behavior that interferes with other spectators of the game. Officials are only responsible for what happens on the ice.',
  correctanswer:"False",
  incorrectanswers: [
    "True"
  ]
},
{ id:'2usa29',
rulelink:'1084688-rule-630-off-sides',
rulenum:'630c',//checked
  question: 'Please indicate the proper face-off location: Intentional offside',
  correctanswer:"End Zone Face-off spot",
  incorrectanswers: [
    "Neutral Zone Face-off spot",
    "Center Ice Face-off spot"
  ]
},

{ id:'2usa30',
rulelink:'1084580-rule-503-linesman',
rulenum:'503(c, d & e)',
  question: 'Which can a linesman NOT stop play for?',
  correctanswer:"A coach taunting an opponent.",
  incorrectanswers: [
    "A goal unobserved by the referee.",
    "Articles thrown on the ice from the players bench."
  ]
},
{ id:'2usa31',
rulelink:'1085038-off-sides',
rulenum:'630d Sit. 34 & 624a',
  question: 'A player in a game where the delayed off-sides rule applies shoots the puck from his defending half of the neutral zone across his opponent’s goal line. A teammate is completely over his attacking blue line before the puck crosses that blue line and is therefore off-side (non-intentional situation). The play is stopped and the face-off is held at the:',
  correctanswer:"Nearest end zone face-off spot of the team icing the puck.",
  incorrectanswers: [
    "Nearest neutral zone face off-spot",
    "Linesman’s choice of face-off spots."
  ]
},
{ id:'2usa32',
rulelink:'1084338-rule-205-change-of-players',
rulenum:'205d',
  question: 'A player serving a penalty on the penalty bench, whose penalty has expired must proceed by way of the ice to the player’s bench. His substitute may start onto the ice at the expiration of the penalty.',
  correctanswer:"False",
  incorrectanswers: [
    "True"
  ]
},
{ id:'2usa33',
rulelink:'1084338-rule-205-change-of-players',
rulenum:'205a',
  question: 'While play is in progress a team is changing players. A player entering the game is accidentally struck by the puck while the player he is changing for is still on the ice. A too many players on the ice minor penalty should be assessed.',
  correctanswer:"False",
  incorrectanswers: [
    "True"
  ]
},
{ id:'2usa34',
rulelink:'1084398-rule-301-stickss',
rulenum:'301e',
  question: 'A player who is carrying a replacement stick to the goalkeeper and is accidentally struck by the puck while in possession of two sticks should be assessed a minor penalty.',
  correctanswer:"False",
  incorrectanswers: [
    "True"
  ]
},
{ id:'2usa35',
rulelink:'1084405-rule-307-equipment-measurement',
rulenum:'307b',
  question: 'A referee may not legally measure a stick without a request from the opposing team.',
  correctanswer:"True",
  incorrectanswers: [
    "False"
  ]
},
{ id:'2usa36',
rulelink:'1084489-rule-411-progressive-suspensions',
rulenum:'411a',
  question: 'Under Rule 411 (progressive suspensions), the major penalties must be for the same infraction to count toward the players’ three-game, five-game or indefinite suspension.',
  correctanswer:"False",
  incorrectanswers: [
    "True"
  ]
},
{ id:'2usa37',
rulelink:'1084402-rule-304-protective-equipment',
rulenum:'304f',
  question: 'A player may wear a clear (non-colored) mouthguard as long as the official is notified prior to the start of the game.',
  correctanswer:"False",
  incorrectanswers: [
    "True"
  ]
},
{ id:'2usa38',
rulelink:'1084335-rule-202-captain-of-team',
rulenum:'202a',
  question: 'The referee notices during warm-ups that all players on one team, including the goalkeepers, have “C”s on their uniforms. This is permitted as long as the team designates one captain and not more than two alternates on the scoresheet prior to the start of the game.',
  correctanswer:"True",
  incorrectanswers: [
    "False"
  ]
},
{ id:'2usa39',
rulelink:'1084584-rule-507-penalty-timekeeper',
rulenum:'507c',
  question: 'To make more room for the players and coaches on the players’ bench, it is permissable for the backup goaltender to occupy the penalty bench',
  correctanswer:"False",
  incorrectanswers: [
    "True"
  ]
},
{ id:'2usa40',
rulelink:'1084718-rule-639-tripping-clipping-leg-checking',
rulenum:'639a(2)',
  question: 'A player dives (leaves his feet) and sweeps the puck away from his opponent. The follow through of the sweeping action causes the opponent to trip and fall to the ice. Because the defending player made contact and swept the puck away before his opponent tripped, a penalty for tripping should NOT be called.',
  correctanswer:"False",
  incorrectanswers: [
    "True"
  ]
},
{ id:'2usa41',
rulelink:'1084477-rule-401-penalties',
rulenum:'401b & 411b',
  question: 'Any team that receives three or more major penalties, or fifteen or more penalties, in the same game shall have its head coach suspended for the team’s next game. However, he is not assessed a game misconduct penalty.',
  correctanswer:"True",
  incorrectanswers: [
    "False"
  ]
},
{ id:'2usa42',
rulelink:'1084645-rule-601-abuse-of-officials-and-other-misconduct',
rulenum:'601e(2)',
  question: 'Depending upon how objectionable it is, an obscene gesture may result in a misconduct or game misconduct penalty.',
  correctanswer:"False",
  incorrectanswers: [
    "True"
  ]
},
{ id:'2usa43',
rulelink:'1084657-rule-612-face-off-locations',
rulenum:'612f',
  question: 'The puck is shot by the attacking team in the neutral zone. It strikes an official and goes directly into the goal. There is no goal and the resulting face-off should take place at the nearest face-off spot to where the puck was shot.',
  correctanswer:"False",
  incorrectanswers: [
    "True"
  ]
},
{ id:'2usa44',
rulelink:'1084660-rule-613-face-off-procedures',
rulenum:'613e',
  question: 'A minor penalty for interference shall be assessed to any player facing-off who makes any physical contact with his opponent’s body by means of his own body or by his stick except in the course of playing the puck after the face-off has been completed.',
  correctanswer:"True",
  incorrectanswers: [
    "False"
  ]
},
{ id:'2usa45',
rulelink:'1085023-head-butting',
rulenum:'619b Sit. 1 & 305b',
  question: 'A player with taped hands injures an opponent during an altercation. During the same altercation he head-butts the same opponent. Because the same opponent was fouled only one match penalty should be assessed.',
  correctanswer:"False",
  incorrectanswers: [
    "True"
  ]
},
{ id:'2usa46',
rulelink:'1085025-high-sticks',
rulenum:'621b Sit. 3',
  question: 'A major penalty and a game misconduct penalty for high sticking should be assessed to a player who checked and who is body checked, as he is falling to the ice, cuts an opponent on the head with his "high" stick?',
  correctanswer:"True",
  incorrectanswers: [
    "False"
  ]
},
{ id:'2usa47',
rulelink:'1084688-rule-630-off-sides',
rulenum:'630d(5)',
  question: 'An attacking player in a game where the delayed off-sides rule applies shoots the puck from the neutral zone and directly on goal with a teammate off-sides. The goalie makes the save and starts to pass the puck to his teammate. The linesman should:',
  correctanswer:"Stop play immediately for an off-side infraction.",
  incorrectanswers: [
    "Allow play to continue if attacking players are attempting to tag-up",
    "Either option depending upon the certainty of the goalkeeper's save."
  ]
},
{ id:'2usa48',
rulelink:'1084660-rule-613-face-off-procedures',
rulenum:'613d',
  question: 'A second face-off violation shall result in a delay of game penalty if it occurs:',
  correctanswer:"By the same team during the same face-off.",
  incorrectanswers: [
    "By the same team anytime during the game.",
    "By the same player anytime during the game."
  ]
},
{ id:'2usa49',
rulelink:'1084662-rule-614-falling-on-puck',
rulenum:'614c',
  question: "A minor penalty for delay of game shall be assessed to any goalkeeper who falls on or gathers the puck into his body and causes a stoppage of play when the puck is outside the boundaries of the goalkeeper's privileged area.",
  correctanswer:"True",
  incorrectanswers: [
    "False"
  ]
},
{ id:'2usa50',
rulelink:'1018530-appendix-iv-official-rink-diagrams',
rulenum:'Rink Diagram',
  question: "The two-inch thick red line outlining the goal crease is considered to be part of the goal crease.",
  correctanswer:"True",
  incorrectanswers: [
    "False"
  ]
}

];

export default QUESTION_U2;
